Western Federation of Miners International Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Records 5268
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Congress of Industrial Organizations - Union Publications, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Report to President Philip Murray, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: May 16-17, 1947. 15 pp.
  - Item 2: Resolution and Report Expelllng the International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers from the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Author: CIO, Executive Board.
    Notes: February 15, 1950. 16 pp.
- National Association of Die Cast Workers - Union Publications, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1939?
  - Item 1: Labor and Production: A Handbook for Stewards, Committesmen and Officers, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: National Association of Die Casting Workers
    Notes: (1939?). 40 pp.
- Industrial Workers of the World - Union Publications, 1905-1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Plain Statement of Its Structure and Principles, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: 40 pp.
  - Item 2: The Coeur d'Alene Strike, 1919; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: Metal Mine Workers Industrial Union no. 800
  - Item 3: Go Slow!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Three Kinds of Strikes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: Lumber Workers' Industrial Union no. 120
  - Item 5: I.W.W. vs. W.F. of M., Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Miners of the Coeur d'Alene District, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Miners of Park City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: What is the I.W.W.?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods. Third revised edition
  - Item 9: Public Opinion: Where Does It Stand on the Question of Amnesty of Political Prisoners, 1923; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Manifesto, 1905; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: Conference of Industrial Unionists
    Notes: To the Workers of the World. January 2-4, 1905.
  - Item 11: The I.W.W.; Its History, Structure and Methods, 1917; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: Vincent St. John
  - Item 12: The Red Light Ticket, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Open Letter to the Department of Justice, 1918; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: Metal Mine Workers Industrial Union no. 800; Thomas Hodges; Joe Kennedy
    Notes: September 19, 1918.
  - Item 14: Miners of the Coeur d'Alene District, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Action Taken By the Jerome Branch Metal Mine Workers Industrial Union no. 800, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 16: Strike Delcared Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 17: Twenty-Five Years of Industrial Unionism, 1930; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: James P. Thompson; Roger N. Baldwin; Ralph Chaplin; C. E. Payne; Tom Connors; F. W. Thompson; Ed Delaney; Clifford B. Ellis; Joseph Wagner; John A. Gahan
- Western Federation of Miners - Union Publications, 1904-1907 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  1904, 1907. Includes photograph and postcard.
  - Item 1: Reply of the Western Federation of Miners to the "Red Book" of the Mine Operators' Association, 1904; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: Category of Crime of the Mine Operators' Association - A Partial List, Slewing 85l Men Murdered in Less Than Four Years. Also known as the "Green Book".
  - Item 2: Western Federation of Miners Parade, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: Photograph
  - Item 3: Statement to the General Public of Bisbee and Vincinity, 1907; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Western Federation of Miners Parade, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: Postcard
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers - Union Correspondence, 1937-1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  1937, 1946, 1947, 1948, 1950
  - Item 1: Letter to All Affiliated Local Unions, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Reid Robinson
    Notes: January 27, 1937. Letter, in the form of a progress report to the Local Unions.
  - Item 2: Increased Production of Vital Non-Ferrous Metals for the Victory Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: War Labor Board Case 218, Union Exhibit XII-A
  - Item 3: Fact-Finding Report, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: May 6, 1946.
  - Item 4: Dear Fellow Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: George T. Kirby
    Notes: Letter to IUMMSW members from George T. Kirby objecting to Reid Robinson and Maurice Travis and advocating the election of opposition candidates, n.d.
  - Item 5: Important Notice All Members of the Ansonia Brass Workers' Union Local 445, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Fred Rubelmann
  - Item 6: An Open Letter for the ABC Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Homer Wilson
    Notes: American Brass Company. February 25, 1947.
  - Item 7: Press Release, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: March 11, 1947.
  - Item 8: Confidential Memo, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Maurice Travis
    Notes: March 25, 1948. Robinson resignation statement, March 10, 1947. Confidential memo to staff members from Maurice Travis outlining the current dangers to the union and the proper policies for the IUMMSW to follow.
  - Item 9: Attention: Max E. Baker, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: F. S. Mulock
    Notes: Midvale Mill and Smeltermen's Union no. 331
  - Item 10: Minority Report of the International Executive Board, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Ken Eckert; W. J. Madill
    Notes: Submitted to the Emergency Conference, May 30, 1948.
  - Item 11: Copy of Letter to Phillip Murray following expulsion of Mine Mill from CIO, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: Letter was never sent
- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers - Union Publications, 1934-1952 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Takes More Than Guns, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Morris Wright; Reid Robinson
    Notes: A Brief History ot the International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers
  - Item 2: Jimmy Higgins' Handbook: A Manual for Shop Stewards, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Wartime Collective Bargaining, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: Report and Recommendations of the Committee on Manpower and Wage Stabilization
  - Item 4: Your Union Is News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: A Guide For Local Publicity Committees
  - Item 5: What Uncle Sam Thinks of Our Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: A Few Government Bouquets for the IUMMSW
  - Item 6: Handbook for Secretaries, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: James J. Leary
    Notes: Instructions and Assistance for Local Union Secretaries and Trustees
  - Item 7: A Trip Through the Office of the Secretary-Treasurer, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Mine-Mill Local Leader, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1948:July)
  - Item 9: Election Returns from Local Unions, 1934; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: October 17, 1934.
  - Item 10: The Union: Specail Supplement, Labor's Victory Program for War and Peace, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: March 27, 1944.
  - Item 11: Vote Nov. 4 For Honest Leadership, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Committee for Unity and Progress
  - Item 12: Sign Here: Not Us Says Mine-Mill, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: press and Education Department
  - Item 13: Memo on Manpower and Wage Policy, 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: July 22, 1942.
  - Item 14: Policy Statement on Taft-Hartley Act, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: International Executive Board
    Notes: July 14, 1947.
  - Item 15: Roll Call for the 44th Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: Local Unions, September 1948.
  - Item 16: Local 890 Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Local 890
  - Item 17: What Does Democracy Mean?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 18: Mine-Mill Coeur d'Alene News, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Coeur d'Alene District Local 18
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1952:June 7)
  - Item 19: Expose, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: The officers of the C.I.O. Local raiding Mine-Mill have this labor history
  - Item 20: Union Songs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 21: Canvassing Committee Minority Report Concerning International Election Held on November 4, 1946, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Harry Krogulski; Dan McKittrick; Charles A. Davis
  - Item 22: In Answer to Brother Robinson's Speech, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 23: In Answer to Brother Robinson's Speech, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 24: In Answer to Brother Robinson's Speech, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 25: In Answer to Brother Robinson's Speech, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 26: Mine-Mill: A Rock of Unionism, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 27: What Does Democracy Mean?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 28: These Are Our Demands in 1952 for a Better Life, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 29: Minutes of the First Meeting Between the Kennecott Joint Negotiating Committee and Company, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: May 26, 1952.
  - Item 30: Miner's Voice, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: Miner's Day Edition, June 13, 1952.
  - Item 31: Miner's Voice, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 32: The Union, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1948:July 5)
  - Item 33: ABC Union News, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1947:May 8)
  - Item 34: Grievance Report, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Provisional Metalworkers Council - Union Publications, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Why So Silent on Travis, Boys?, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: Provisional Metalworkers Council, CIO
    Notes:
  - Item 2: Metal Workers Guide, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.1 (1947)
  - Item 3: Metal Workers Guide, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: no.1 (1947). Copy 2
  - Item 4: The Progressive Metalworker, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.1:no.14 (1948:Mar. 23)
  - Item 5: Industrial Union Reporter, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.12:no.5 (1948:April 5)
  - Item 6: Industrial Union Reporter, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.12:no.8 (1948:May 17)
  - Item 7: Industrial Union Reporter, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.12:no.9 (1948:May 31)
  - Item 8: Shipyard Worker, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.11:no.33 (1947:May 19)
  - Item 9: Shipyard Worker, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.11:no.33 (1947:May 19). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Shipyard Worker, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.11:no.34 (1947:june 2)
  - Item 11: Statement on the Resignation of Reid Robinson as President of the Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: John J. Driscoll; Angelo Verdu; John J. Mankowski
    Notes: March 12, 1947.
  - Item 12: Statement on the Resignation of Reid Robinson as President of the Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: March 12, 1947. Copy 2
  - Item 13: A Problem That You, The Rank and File Members, Will Have To Solve, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: George Wilde; Edwin T. Lauritzen
  - Item 14: Time for a Change, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 15: Where Do You Stand?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations - Union Correspondence, 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  1943 and 1950. Several letters pertaining to the administration of District No. 6 (Connecticut) IUMMSW by the International. Executive Board of the CIO during 1943 and a letter to members concerning the Investigation of communism in the IUMMSW.
- H.S. McCluskey - Union Correspondence, 1909-1917 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  1909 and 1917. Approximately 30 pieces of correspondence to and from E. S. McClusky, IUMMSW organizer during the 1917 strike at Jerome, Arizona. The letters deal with IWW-IUMMSW rivalry and the "deportation" of "IWW agitators" from Jerome during July 1917.
- Bingham Miners' Union Number 67 - Record Book, 1904-1907 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Bound Volume. November 26, 1904-May 25, 1907.
  - Item 1: Minute Book, 1904-1907 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Bingham Miners' Union No. 67
    Notes: November 26, 1904 to May 25, 1907
- Bingham Miners' Union Number 67 - Record Book, 1907-1908 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Bound Volume. June 1, 1907-December 19, 1908.
  - Item 1: Minute Book, 1907-1908 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: June 1, 1907 to December 19, 1908.
- Bingham Miners' Union Number 67 - Correspondence, 1903-1919 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Includes Photographs. 1903, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1916, 1919
- Butte Miners' Union Number 1 - Record Book, 1925-1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  December 20, 1925-September 20, 1930
  - Item 1: Minute Book, 1925-1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Author: Butte Miners' Union No. 1
    Notes: December 20, 1925 to July 20, 1930.
- Butte Miners' Union Number 1 - Organization Book, 1927-1931 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Minute Book, 1927-1931 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Author: Butte Miners' Union No. 1 Miner's Organizing Committee
    Notes: November 11, 1927 to March 13, 1931.
- American Zinc Company of Illinois, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Press Releases and letters to employers dealing with the refusal of local union officers to sign non-communist affidavits in 1948 and an NLRB election and strike in 1949.
- Anaconda Copper Mining Company, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Mining Department Safety Rules., 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: Anaconda Copper Mining Co.
    Notes: January 1937.
  - Item 2: Anaconda Copper Mining Company: Its Properties and Operations in Montana., Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Bridgeport Brass Company, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job at Bridgeport Brass, 1946; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: Bridgeport Brass Company
- Colorado Mine Operators' Association, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Criminal Record of the Western Federation of Miners: Coeur d'Alene to Cripple Creek, 1894-1904, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: Colorado Mine Operators' Association
    Notes: The "Red Book"
- Copper Country Commercial Club of Michigan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Strike Investigation, 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Copper Country Commercial Club of Michigan
- Eagle-Picher Mining and Smelting Company, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Press Releases and Judicial opinions by the NLRB and the U. S. Supreme Court in the case of the Eagle-Picher Co. v. IUMMSW. Case continued for ten years.
- Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Letter to employees explaining Kennecott's termination of relations with the IUMMSW as a result of the refusal of Mine Mill officers to sign non-Communist affidavits.
- Montana Power Company, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Her Majesty Montana: High Lights in the History of a State Fifty Years Old in 1939, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: C. W. Towne
    Notes: The Pioneer Period: 1743-1877. A series of 28 radio broadcasts.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Scovill, You, and Your Job, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Scovill Manufacturing Company
- Scovill Manufacturing Company - "The Bulletin", 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  January-May 1947
  - Item 1: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1947:Jan. 6). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.2 (1947:Jan. 13). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.3 (1947:Jan. 20). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 4: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1947:Jan. 27). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.5 (1947:Feb. 3). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 6: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.6 (1947:Feb. 10). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 7: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1947:Feb. 17). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 8: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.9 (1947:Mar. 3). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 9: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.10 (1947:Mar. 10). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 10: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.11 (1947:Mar. 17). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 11: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.12 (1947:Mar. 24). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 12: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.13 (1947:Mar. 31). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 13: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.16 (1947:Apr. 21). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 14: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.17 (1947:Apr. 28). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 15: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.18 (1947:May 5). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 16: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.19 (1947:May 12). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 17: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.20 (1947:May 19). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 18: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.31:no.21 (1947:May 26). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company - "The Bulletin", 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  June-December 1947
  - Item 1: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.22 (1947:June 2). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.23 (1947:June 9). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.24 (1947:June 16). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 4: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.25 (1947:June 23). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.26 (1947:June 30). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 6: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.27 (1947:July 14). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 7: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.28 (1947:Aug. 4). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 8: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.29 (1947:Aug. 18). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 9: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.30 (1947:Sept. 1). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 10: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.32 (1947:Oct. 6). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 11: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.33 (1947:Oct. 20). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 12: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.34 (1947:Nov. 3). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 13: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.35 (1947:Nov. 17). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 14: The Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.31:no.37 (1947:Dec. 15). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company - "The Bulletin", 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  January-May 1948
  - Item 1: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1948:Jan. 5). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.2 (1948:Jan. 19). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.3 (1948:Feb. 2). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 4: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.4 (1948:Feb. 16). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.5 (1948:Mar. 1). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 6: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.6 (1948:Mar. 15). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 7: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.7 (1948:Apr. 5). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 8: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.8 (1948:Apr. 19). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 9: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.9 (1948:May 3). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 10: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.32:no.10 (1948:May 17). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company - "The Bulletin", 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  June-December 1948
  - Item 1: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.11 (1948:June 7). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 2: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.12 (1948:June 21). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.13 (1948:July 5). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 4: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.32:no.14 (1948:July 19). Published by the Scovill Manufacturing Company for its Employees.
  - Item 5: The Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)